Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Camel of other things.
We're on Earth, a legendary!
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners.
Cause if you're wanted,
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise,
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day.
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first.
I'll put it be so bad.
Just a bit first.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel.
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed?
I'm done playing through with the wave.
In every world I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
And here we go!
We go!
Move it!
Please! Stop him!
He's getting away with our money!
Somebody do something!
Just stay out of my way, got it?
Because you don't want to see what I'll
do to this girl if you try to be a hero.
Your Majesty.
Wait, don't go that way!
You shouldn't involve
yourself with such a thing.
This is not our responsibility.
Please wait!
Queen Otohime.
Who's that?
Don't come any closer, I'll shoot!
I warned you!
I missed?
Dammit, goodbye!
I got you!
Wait, isn't that Queen Otohime?
My hair!
Hurry, doctor!
Your highness, let me take a look.
It's fractured, I'm afraid.
She hit him once and broke her hand?
It's fine.
Queen Otohime!
The queen?
Why would you do something as foolish and
selfish as robbing your fellow people?
What do you care?
Like a rich member of the
royal family could understand.
I got ten kids waiting at home, and all
they do is cry because they're hungry!
All the more reason!
No! Queen Otohime!
You must stop hitting him, please!
They're much too delicate.
You will only make your injury worse!
I don't care!
I have to do this!
Even if my hand must shatter to
pieces, he will learn his lesson!
Do you think your children would
be happy if they knew the truth?
If they knew their father was a thief?
You should be trying to live your
life in a way that makes them proud.
However, I owe you an apology.
Please forgive me.
Even though I'm your queen,
I've been completely
ignorant to the hardships
that one of my subjects
has been forced to endure.
My heart can't take it.
Your worries and your
pain, they're killing me.
You must have had a reason for doing this.
I don't know.
It's not that I wanted to.
But I, I felt like there was no other way.
Somebody sent fire to my
store and stole all my money.
We couldn't save anything
before we hurt down.
Just like that, I didn't have a job.
My debts started piling up,
and now my kids are starving.
I'm sorry that happened.
And I understand.
I really do, but...
It's wrong!
If you do to others what was done
to you, the cycle will never end!
I'm sorry!
No, I'm sorry.
We weren't there for you in your time of
need, so that makes us accountable as well.
Your Highness,
it's really not your fault, but that's a
terribly generous thing for you to say.
It's still wrong, though!
I know, I know!
Then don't do it!
You've changed me, and my whole life!
Thank you so much, after seeing
how much you cried for me!
I'll never steal again!
I know that you won't!
Best of luck in the future!
We're so lucky to have a member
of the royal family who's
not afraid to share the troubles
of common people like us.
She nearly had me crying along with her,
though I certainly hope she
doesn't break her hand next time.
Our Queen Otohime is a one-of-a-kind
ruler, I can tell you that much.
She has such a kind heart.
And look there!
Even the children of
the kingdom adore her.
Queen Otohime!
I'll do everything I can to
protect your smiling faces.
Your nose is running terribly!
If I don't reprimand you for it, who will?
You look ridiculous with mucus
dribbling out of just one side.
It's more dignified to
dribble from both nostrils.
Such a tender moment!
I guess so.
No one was more passionate or loving.
Every day, Queen Otohime descended
from the palace to address the nation.
That day was no different.
The time has come for us to relocate
the Ryugu kingdom to the surface.
Our skins are different colors,
and we do not look the same.
These are the things the
humans say in order to
avoid understanding us and
our unique way of life.
But that's why we should move,
to understand each other.
Our worlds are 10,000 meters apart,
so that is also the distance
between our ways of thinking.
I know you're afraid.
After all, the humans who come to
our island are pirates and criminals.
And the humans who buy our people from
kidnappers like them are
cruel and Corrupt nobles
it's true that our only exposure to humans
has been negative but That doesn't mean we
can judge all humans the same I believe in
my heart That there are
good ones among them
as well and thus to
improve relations we Must
move our kingdom to be
under the same Sun it
is my goal to express our Intention to
relocate above sea level at this year's world
summit but in order to
do that I Need all of
you to sign while uh I
admit it sounds like a
good idea in theory
but just the thought Of
living near humans is
well I understand how
you feel however this
is our chance to make
a Real change rather
than suffering in silence
Please look I'm
sorry but no it's no
use History can't be fought so easily
Hello everyone, I'm home!
I'm home, Shirahoshi!
I hope you can forgive me, darling.
Mommy didn't mean to be so late!
Even with your nose running on
one side, you're still beautiful.
We stayed with her the entire time you
were gone so she'd feel safe, Mother.
It's true, Mother, we did?
I have such brave sons.
But what happened to your hand?
Are you okay?
Oh, don't worry, dear.
It's nothing.
See?
To ensure you all have a
bright future, I would suffer.
So much worse than this.
If Queen Otohime wants
to make announcements,
she really should do them by video
rather than going down there in person.
Unfortunately, thanks to
her strong observation Haki,
Doing something like that would
go against her very nature.
She would rather win the hearts of the
citizens in person than from the palace.
It's one of Otohime's guiding principles.
Not even I can change that.
She's constantly putting
her life at risk with all
those human pirates coming
and going on the island.
We know you're on good
terms with Whitebeard,
and to some extent his influence
can protect her while she's there.
But anything could happen.
That is a fact of which
she is all too aware.
And yet it does nothing to deter her.
For the world Otohime dreams of
Is far more than a simple fantasy.
After all, unifying our peoples was
also the ambition of our ancestors.
Although they were never able
to make that vision a reality?
What?
I'm afraid that I don't
follow your majesty
I can't stop Otohime from
doing what she thinks is right.
So it's up to you to keep her safe!
Yes, sir.
This Queen Otohime certainly
seemed unique, if nothing else.
Sounds like she was a crybaby, too.
Did you inherit that from her?
Um, yes, I suppose I did.
Hold on, you used to be a
soldier for the kingdom?
When you grow up in the Fishman District,
where you know nothing but fighting,
there aren't a lot of career
path options available to you.
You don't say. That's rough.
Is that where you're from, Hachi?
It sounds like a pretty bad neighborhood.
It was.
Believe me.
Originally, it was an orphanage for
children with no living relatives.
But in time, the orphanage became too
much for the administrators to handle.
Before long,
it became a lawless area that caught the
eye of delinquents from
all over the island.
Back then, Fisher Tiger was the
closest thing we had to a leader.
but he left to have his own adventures.
I'd been his second in command, but
I went on to join Neptune's army.
And despite being fishmen,
Macro and some others started
helping the kidnappers.
As for everyone else,
they all left, following
their own pursuits.
Until one day.
Please, give them back!
Oh, you almost had them that time.
Hey, knock it off!
Do you realize how hard it was for
her to get all those signatures?
Yeah, and you realize I don't care, right?
Hey, cut it out!
You fishman district reject! Huh?
You think you're better than
me because of where I'm from?
Let go of me!
You got it backwards, pal.
I'm the captain of the Arlong
Pirates, and you're just a nobody.
I clean up all the human
garbage you let run wild.
Pirates so pathetic, they can't
even breathe in the water.
You guys in Neptune's
army should be faking us.
Maybe I should beat a donation out of you.
Please, I'm in trouble over here.
He's gonna kill me, Boss Jinbei. Jinbei.
All right, punk.
Just put the rookie down and walk away.
He's weak, but he's one of my men.
And as for those papers you've taken,
And they may not mean anything to us, but
they're quite important to her majesty.
Give them back.
That's Boss G.
May of Neptune's army.
He'll help us.
Yeah, they call you Boss.
How'd you get that kind of respect?
Sounds more like the title of a
gang leader than a soldier, though.
I told you to let him go, Arlong.
All right, fine.
Here.
So are we all good now, brother?
Brother?
It's been a while, but I can always tell
when someone's from the Fistman district.
Don't lump me in with you.
You went off and became a lousy pirate.
You're scum.
Don't call me that, brother.
Then how about trash?
Oh, that's it.
Doesn't matter where we're from.
You can't talk to me like that.
Hey.
Hey, everyone.
I can.
Fisher Tiger's come home.
I don't believe it. Tiger's back.
He's here. Where was the trip?
It's brother time.
Finally made it back.
Hi, Jinbei. And Arlong.
It sure looks like you
two have been doing well.
That was quite a lengthy voyage you took.
Yeah, an eventful one, too.
Now that you're here, you can see my ship.
Later.
First, I need to go to the Ryugu Palace.
I can show you the way.
He has no need for a lousy pirate.
Huh?
That's not how Big Brother
feels about me at all!
Come on, guys. Don't fight.
You're telling me you're
going to free the slaves?
I can't stand it anymore.
The thought of our people living a
nightmare even as we're speaking right now,
our people are being treated like animals.
Yes, but my mind's made up.
Tell me, why are you
so adamant about this?
What did you see? on your trip.
I saw human nature.
Not long after that, Tiger made his move.
This is bad!
What's the problem?
Oh, God, I found you, boss.
It's about Tiger. It seems he...
he attacked the Celestial Dragons.
No, that can't be true.
Fischer-Tiger unleashed Alto war
on the Holy Land of Mariegeois.
For freeing the slaves,
he forever became a hero to our people
and a criminal to the world government.
Consider this my resignation
from the army. Jinbei!
You would walk away from your sworn duty?
Much to my surprise, I've enjoyed
my role as this island's protector.
However, my obligation to this kingdom
does not outweigh my debt of honor.
It looks like Big Brother Ty
has finally made his move.
All right, Olog Pirates, from
here on, we work for Fisher Tiger.
Let's go, men!
Before long,
every ruffian from the fishman district
had assembled a fight by his side.
How does it feel to be lumped
in with lousy pirate scum?
It's us against the world from now on.
If you're truly ready for
the days ahead, then step up.
All who accepted the sun mark
that day became brothers.
It was a symbol that enveloped
the brand given to slaves.
No longer could anyone distinguish
which of us had always been free?
And which of us had to fight
to reclaim that freedom?
And that's how a bunch of lowlifes
from the fishbed district rose up!
As the sun pirates.
It's hard to believe he
really went through with it.
His actions have only created
more problems for Fishman Island.
It will be quite some time before we'll
welcome back to the world's summit.
I don't even know where
to begin to fix this.
But we share the blame.
Remember, we just couldn't
bring ourselves to stop him.
Tell me why are you so
adamant about this what
did you see on your
trip I saw human nature
Because I understood the depth of his
suffering a scream of his
soul it was unbearable
Extra! Extra!
Read all about it!
Wow, he's such a badass.
Fighting the Celestial Dragons?
Talk about balls.
Yeah, that makes it official.
Fisher Tiger is a true hero. Whoa!
A fish man's gonna wind
up in the history books.
Listen, gather around.
Hey, it's Queen Otohime.
What is it now?
We have cowered, and hid,
and run, and yet for what?
What have we gained from this?
What good has this path
done for our people?
We can't simply turn our
backs on the entire world.
to cut off all humans it will doom us some
humans are bad yes but not all of them now
we must learn to live
in harmony with humanity
and together we can grow with them under
the bright nourishing
sun grow with them huh
yeah that's just too
much to ask hey you two
sign here but i can't i'm sorry please
the whole island tied as a hero to
us for what he did you know it's just
we know his actions might turn the
humans against us but it's their
fault they brought it on themselves so
we can't sign i know how you feel but
in seven years or even 15 years you
have to think about that future there
will come a day when we will be able
to participate in the world summit
again you have to sign for our future
i'm begging you i'm telling you
fisher tiger gets it this is how you
represent the fishman district he went
head to head with the celestial dragons
and he freaking won way to stick
it to those disgusting humans it's
just like arlong used to say the
only good human is a dead one yeah
now put him in their place the
sun pirates are so cool i Sailing
the sea and slamming the docent
down on every dumb human they meet.
It's awesome! You know what?
If we were a little stronger,
then I bet we could join them!
We'll get strong!
Then, we will!
Take back the sea, Sun Pirates!
Kill all those worthless humans!
Hey boss!
Boss, there's an enemy ship! Boss!
Hey, hey guys!
Did you hear me?
We got a crisis!
Shut up, Hachi! Crap!
Calm down.
Just tell us what's going on.
Is it the Navy? Must be.
They were flying their flag out there.
There's no mistake!
Those are the Sun Pirates!
Kill Fisher Tiger!
Ha ha ha ha!
Real nice aim there!
Fire!
What are you doing?
Shoot them dead!
We're trying, but they're
swimming too fast!
Pardon me, gents.
You fish-man bastards!
Return the slaves, damn it! Surrender!
If you play ball,
they'll drop the charges!
We're Admirals!
They're bursting up through
the bottom of the shaft!
What?
Give us back the slaves and this will end!
Do you even realize the
serious crime you've committed?
How dare you turn on humans!
Know your place, you disgusting fishmen!
What was that?
Go on now.
Let's hear you say that again!
Please, somebody help me!
So slavery's perfectly legal,
but freeing slaves is a crime?
And Queen Otohime thinks
you deserve a chance.
Not that you'd give us one!
Now, fire!
Blow him to pieces, men!
We know that you're hiding the slaves!
And now you're gonna die for
the havoc you've wrought!
Oh, what the hell?
These slaves mentioned.
He's...
he's a monster!
What proof do you possibly have
that we're hiding them on board?
Go on and check all of us if you want to.
But from what I understand, these
slaves should have a brand on them.
Do you see that mark on
any of us? Wait! Stop!
Put me down!
Help me!
I won't kill you. Don't worry.
I'm not a savage like you.
All right, guys.
Take all their money and food
and get back to the ship.
Being human is a sin.
And so, you were born deserving execution.
No, stop.
DROP DASH!
Vice Admiral, Rear Admiral Cutter
from the G2 branch has been defeated.
Huh?
Why did he engage them?
I only wanted to report on
their current whereabouts.
If you get close enough to see them,
well,
that's apparently all it takes before their
entire crew surrounds you in the water.
Oh, scary.
Fishman, guess we should
have expected that.
Okay, do you have any intel you can share?
Well, the way it looks, Arlong
and his men are part of the crew.
And they were responsible for the raids
in the area surrounding Fishman Island.
But we have yet to fight them on land,
so it's hard to tell how strong they are.
Arlong?
Right, I've heard of him.
There's another dangerous
one on their crew.
He's as big as Fisher
Tiger and just as brutal.
Didn't catch his name.
Well, sounds like a real mess.
Ow! That hurt!
What's the big deal?
Why the hell do you care if we kill
one or two of those inferior creatures?
It's not about them.
You're both going too far.
Look, we're not a group of killers.
We're better than that.
And don't you forget it.
But look, brother.
Sorry, I mean boss.
These humans have no such compunction.
They are actively out to kill you.
So can you blame us?
Of course we might go too far
from time to time. We're mad!
Do you want to be like the humans?
Killing someone is to kill
a part of your own soul!
We are not seeking revenge
for the discrimination here.
And that's not what Marie
Joie was about either.
I might have broken that
stupid unspoken rule,
but I only did it to free those slaves.
The Sun Pirates are driven by the
idea of liberation and freedom,
not spiteful retribution.
Seeking vengeance against the
humans only creates a vicious cycle.
Violence begets violence, and I will
not be responsible for more tragedy.
We'll end up condemning the next
generation of fishmen to war with humanity.
Can't you see that?
We will fight and rob those who come
after us, but we won't cross the line.
We will not become killers.
Listen, brother.
I think you're overlooking
one simple fact.
Violence always begets violence, you say?
Well, not if they're all dead.
Who's gonna fight back if we kill them?
We'll massacre the animals and force
all the women and children to watch.
Terrifying the idea of revenge
right out of their minds.
All we have to do is show them how
powerful and ruthless we can be and then
they'll be paralyzed with terror they
will never what the hell is your problem
It's great what Queen Otohime is trying to
accomplish though
understandably to For her,
there's no difference
between Arlong and me.
Honestly, there's only one
thing that I'm really afraid of.
My own mind.
Up ahead, there's a pirate ship!
Looks like a big one.
I'm guessing they want to take
us on to prove themselves.
We are really racking up the enemies.
Well, I say we seek their ship.
Best to make an example of them.
We were engaged in
combat on a daily basis.
Criminals hunted by the world government.
Meanwhile, Queen Otohime waged her own
stubborn form of battle against the world.
Sign here!
No, we won't!
We don't want to live with humans!
Please sign!
Hey!
The government put out a
bounty on Boss Tai and Jinbei!
Seriously?
Wow, 230 million bearings!
Jinbei's got 76 million on his head!
Wanted posters!
Look, they raised the
reward on them again!
Even the world government
is scared of them!
Yeah, yeah!
They're gonna sink the entire navy!
I need you to sign it!
Let me go, your majesty!
See the next three years unfolded
in a similar manner and then one day
we came across a young girl on an
island Mister we could use your help
with something this girl here she
escaped from Marie Joie with the
rest of us back when you liberated
us from slavery three years ago here
Look
She hasn't seen her parents in many years
And her home's far away We would like to
help I'm sure they miss her But it's highly
doubtful we can safely cross the ocean
I'm Koala and I'm 11 years
old Thanks for saving
me I'll do my best not to
cause you any more trouble
I know she's a kid But
she's still a disgusting
human Why the hell would you
let her on board with us?
Just drop it, Orlang.
I'll drop this ugly brat!
Quit smiling, dammit!
Orlang, no!
Calm down!
Let go, Hachi!
I'm not done yet! He's right.
It is creepy how she won't stop smiling.
Huh? You?
What are you...
I'm sorry.
I'm a hard worker.
I'll clean, and I don't
need to take a break.
So please don't hit me. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'll give it my best.
Stop.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean it.
You're bleeding.
I'm sorry.
I promise that I'll never cry.
Just please don't kill me.
It's all right.
Are you scared of us?
Yes, but I really miss my mother,
so I made myself get on board.
I won't stop cleaning.
I know if I do, you'll think
I'm useless and kill me.
But I'm a hard worker,
so please let me live.
Well, what'd you expect?
The kid was raised a slave.
Think about what she's seen.
I'm sure plenty of her friends got killed.
And probably just for crying or
getting caught taking a break.
She's spent her whole life being
afraid that she might be next.
Can you blame her for not trusting anyone?
Boss?
Pick up this brat.
I want her brought to my room.
What's he doing in there?
Lecturing her won't do any good.
The poor kid's too far gone.
Boss, what are you doing to her?
Bandage her.
It may have hurt,
but she'd never get past the pain of
being a slave with that mark on her.
Hey, kid, you still alive?
Oh, good, you're awake.
Oh, I guess I passed out.
I'm sorry, but I didn't cry, did I?
So you don't need to kill me.
I promise you, I'll never cry.
So please, let me live.
It's okay for you to cry.
We are nothing like those
evil celestial dragons
so don't you dare act
like we are now watch.
No killing.
Not now, not ever.
Is everyone with me? Yeah!
No matter how far the journey,
we're taking this girl back home.
Thank you.